<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ivan Klimchuk</title>
    <link>https://klimchuk.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ivan Klimchuk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 06:00:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://klimchuk.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog reincarnation</title>
      <link>https://klimchuk.com/notes/blog-reincarnation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 06:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://klimchuk.com/notes/blog-reincarnation/</guid>
      <description>As it was before Once upon a time, at the very beginning, the site worked on my own Alroniks CMS, then there was the Dockpad static sites generator (the project died) after there was an attempt to launch the site on MODX, but it was unsuccessful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dukora and the upside down house </title>
      <link>https://klimchuk.com/places/dukora/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://klimchuk.com/places/dukora/</guid>
      <description>At the weekend we decided to go somewhere with the child and decided to go to the village Dukora, which is not far from Minsk.
This is one of several famous estates in the vicinity of Minsk. At the entrance, there is a restored gateway, inside which there are a cash register and a souvenir shop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam and a trip to the conference</title>
      <link>https://klimchuk.com/places/amsterdam-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://klimchuk.com/places/amsterdam-2019/</guid>
      <description>In March, I was invited to speak at the MODX rally in Amsterdam.
He threw things in his backpack and drove off. The trip was not the easiest, ** five ** flights in 3 days!
The trip was purely working, I prepared a report along the way, mounted a podcast, and did other routine things, so there wasn’t much time around to look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate Manifesto</title>
      <link>https://klimchuk.com/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://klimchuk.com/donate/</guid>
      <description>I started my blog 10 years ago to talk about the technology I work with and also to share my thoughts about the world. Over the past 10 years I have gained experience both professionally and in life, and now I have a lot to talk about.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>